# Wilza Aryeetey

Product Designer UX/ UI Designer Georgia

[Portfolio link]
[LinkIn link]

jwilza07@gmail.com 857-615-3962

## **SKILLS**

### **Prototyping Tools**

Figma

Sketch

GitHub

InVision

Photoshop

HTML/CSS

**JavaScript** 

**Usability Hub** 

#### **UX Methods**

Persona

Branding

Prototyping

Card Sorting

Wireframing

**Usability Testing** 

Preference Testing

Competitive Analysis

#### Languages

English

Spansih

Haitian Creole

## **SUMMARY**

I am a user experience designer with a nursing background focused on human-centered solutions. I enjoy the process of collecting data from user research and usability testings as means to design relevant and impactful products for both users and stakeholders.

Having worked in the healthcare field, I know how to connect the dots and collaborate with diverse groups of people to come up with effective solutions.

## **PROJECTS**

**Connect** in progress

Designing a cloud storage prototype that enabled users to create files, share documents, and access stored data. Conducting preference testings, usability testings, and modified the high-fidelity mock-up accordingly. Utilitzing Google Forms, Figma, and UsabilityHub.

The Loft in progress

Due to the coronavirus pandemic, social distancing has had a direct effect on social interaction, along with mental and physical health. Designing a video conferencing platform that consisted of new inovative features, such as the white board and group huddle sessions. Working in Sketch and Invision.

## **EXPERIENCES**

Thinkful Oct 2019-Present

#### **Product Designer Apprentice**

- Created high-fidelity mockups, designed interactive prototypes, and conducted usability testing throughout the product development process
- Learned and designed best practice mobile and web design patterns

Northside Hospital

Aug 2017-Aug 2019

#### **Registered Nurse**

- Ensured patient safety using critical nursing judgment
- Evaluated need for referrals and provided hand off reports in a timely manner

Good Samaritan Medical Center

May 2016-June 2017

#### **Registered Nurse**

- Provided patient centered care on a Med Surg. Unit
- Provided preoperative and postoperative care to patients

## **EDUCATION**

Curry College, Milton, MA Bachelor of Science in Nursing Feb 2014-May 2015

College of the Holy Cross, Worcester, MA Bachelor of Visual Arts

Sept 2007-May 11

References available upon request.